# **ASHWIN SINGH**

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT

- **Q** 647-823-8722
- 🔼 Ashwin.Singh.087@gmail.com
- AshwinSingh.dev
- /in/AshwinSingh087
- 🦰 /<u>Ashwin087</u>

#### **PROFILE**

I am a detail-oriented Front-End Developer with a passion for building practical and efficient apps. My previous experience as a policy analyst and material planner allows me to take a design and build a program from the ground up, down to the last detail. My curiosity for solving problems and learning fuels my drive to write clear and concise code.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### JUNO COLLEGE

OCT 2020 - JULY 2021

- Immersive Bootcamp
- Web Development & JavaScript

# **SENECA COLLEGE**

JAN 2017 - DEC 2017

• Government Relations

#### YORK UNIVERSITY **SEPT 2011 - JUNE 2015**

• Kinesiology and Health Science

#### **SKILLS**







**JavaScript** 

**Firebase** 







React





#### **PROJECTS**

# DAILY CRYPTO UPDATE []





ES6 JavaScript | SASS | Rest API | Paired Programming Searchable cryptocurrency site, the highlighting feature is an accessible auto-suggest search bar users can select from.

## ARTIST DISCOGRAPHY 🗹 😱



React | Firebase | Rest API | HTML 5 | CSS 3

Interactive site where users can find an artist's discography and save their favorite albums which are stored on Firebase.

#### DAILY WEATHER APP [7]





Jauery | Rest API | HTML 5 | CSS 3

Displaying searched city's weather information with a focus on modal functionality and error handling.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **WORK MATERIAL PLANNER**

Bombardier Aerospace | Feb 2019 - June 2020

- Worked cross-functionally with other departments including engineering and production to resolve issues that would prevent the team from fulfilling their deliverables within the 5-day work flow.
- Managed station's work flow to ensure timely delivery of priorities and commitments including electronic material management using SAP and proactively procuring required materials.
- · Managed logistic inquiries by addressing and resolving issues that occurred, advising other departments about proper procedures and correct next steps, and expediting urgent deliverables.

#### **JUNIOR POLICY ANALYST**

Ontario Public Service | Sept 2017 - Dec 2017

- Led the development of a joint ministry pilot project which included determining the approach, structuring the program, drafting all necessary documents, and facilitating the approval process with senior management.
- Liaised with other divisions and ministry partners to coordinate program development and implementation, provide opportunities for engagement and updates about recent developments on key files.